Guide to the New York State College of Human Ecology records, 1900-2017
Cornell University, New York State College of Human Ecology records,
- Series II. Dean's Files
  - E. Alan Mathios (2008-2018)
    - 1. Subject Files
      - Cornell Undergraduate Information Competency Initiative, 2010 (Box 126, Folder 11)
      - Task Force - Graduate education, 2009-2011 (Box 126, Folder 12)
      - Task Force - Leadership education for undergraduates, 2011-04 (Box 126, Folder 13)
      - Learning outcome assessment, 2012 (Box 126, Folder 14)
      - Task Force - management programs, 2009-2010 (Box 126, Folder 15)
      - Task Force - Undergraduate leadership development, outreach, community engagement, and translational research, 2009 (Box 126, Folder 16)
      - Task Force - Undergraduate research, 2009-2012 (Box 126, Folder 17)
      - Task Force - Video Note, 2009 (Box 126, Folder 18)
      - Urban semester program, 2007 (Box 126, Folder 19)
      - Unified Statistical Department, 2009-2010 (Box 126, Folder 20)
      - Cornell Population Program, 2007-2011 (Box 126, Folder 21)
      - Cornell Population Program, 2011 (Box 126, Folder 22)
      - Cornell Population Program, 2010-2011 (Box 126, Folder 23)
      - New York State Health Foundationn Grant - final report, 2008 (Box 126, Folder 24)
      - Office of Chidren and Family Services, 2003 (Box 126, Folder 25)
      - Budget reductions - College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, 2009-2010 (Box 126, Folder 26)
      - Budget reductions - Governors, 2009-2010 (Box 126, Folder 27)
      - Budget reductions - Provost, 2009-2010 (Box 126, Folder 28)
      - Budget reductions - Provost, 2009-2010 (Box 126, Folder 29)
      - Human Development Administration, 2007-2008 (Box 126, Folder 30)
      - Graduate students - IGERT Program, 2011 (Box 126, Folder 31)
      - Student - Elwood, Scot, 2003 (Box 126, Folder 32)
      - Undergraduate advising, 2012 (Box 126, Folder 33)
      - Survey - Seniors, 2012 (Box 126, Folder 34)
      - Survey - Employees, 2011 (Box 126, Folder 34)
      - Survey - Attending and non-attending students, 2012 (Box 126, Folder 34)
      - Local Government Leadership Institute of New York, 2009 (Box 126, Folder 35)
      - Data security, 2011 (Box 126, Folder 36)
      - Cornell University - "A Marketing Opportunity and Image Analysis" Volume IV: Research Summary and Recommendations by Maguire Associates, 1999 (Box 126, Folder 37)
      - Cornell Program in Infrastructure Policy (CPIP), 2013 (Box 126, Folder 38)
      - Cornell Institute for Public Affairs (CIPA), 2012-2013 (Box 126, Folder 39)
      - CIPA, 2011-2012 (Box 126, Folder 40)
      - CIPA, 2010-2011 (Box 126, Folder 41)
      - CIPA, 2001-2003 (Box 126, Folder 42)
      - CIPA charter and core faculty meeting, 2010 (Box 126, Folder 43)
      - Cornell Cooperative Extension - strategic directions, 2008-12 (Box 126, Folder 44)
      - Cornell Cooperative Extension - administration stakeholder map, 2014 (Box 126, Folder 44)
      - Cornell Cooperative Extension - New York City lease, 2004-2008 (Box 126, Folder 45)
      - Cornell Cooperative Extension - New York City programs, 2014-2015 (Box 126, Folder 46)
      - Cornell Cooperative Extension - New York State Community Health Partnership, 2009 (Box 126, Folder 47)
      - Cornell Cooperative Extension - Carneigie Community Engagement Classification, 2010 (Box 126, Folder 48)
      - Cornell Cooperative Extension - New York City extension analysis, 2007 (Box 126, Folder 49)
      - EnHANCE - Engaging Health, Agriculture and Nutrition through the Cornell Experience, 2010 (Box 126, Folder 50)
      - Service level agreement - facilities services, 2015 (Box 126, Folder 51)
      - Council for Agricultural Research Extension, and Teaching (CARET), 2012 (Box 126, Folder 52)
      - Cornell Language Acquisition Lab, 2004 (Box 126, Folder 53)
      - Claire Forest operations, 2006 (Box 126, Folder 54)
      - Proposed School of Public Policy, 2012 (Box 126, Folder 55)
      - Strategic Plan - College, 2011-2012 (Box 126, Folder 56)
      - Strategic Plan - University, 2010 (Box 126, Folder 57)
      - Strategy for the Future of the College of Human Ecology, 2012 (Box 126, Folder 58)
      - Active learning classrooms, 2014 (Box 127, Folder 5)
      - Animal care and use program (ACUPAC), 2011 (Box 127, Folder 6)
      - Art collection, 2000-2012 (Box 127, Folder 7)
      - Bronfrenbrenner Center for Translational Research (BCTR) Administration, 2007-2013 (Box 127, Folder 8)
      - BCTR University Governing Board, 2007 (Box 127, Folder 9)
      - BCTR Porgram on Applied Demographics, 2007-2010 (Box 127, Folder 10)
      - BCTR grants, 2007 (Box 127, Folder 11)
      - BCTR ACT for Youth Center of Excellence, 2012 (Box 127, Folder 12)
      - CAD labs, 1995-2010 (Box 127, Folder 13)
      - Capital Planning, 2013 (Box 127, Folder 14)
      - Capital Planning, 2002-1010 (Box 127, Folder 15)
      - Carnegie community engagement classification questions, 2009 (Box 127, Folder 16)
      - Cornell Center for a Sustainable Future, 2008 (Box 127, Folder 17)
      - Cornell Farmworker Program, 2008-2009 (Box 127, Folder 18)
      - Child Development in Human Ecology, 2008 (Box 127, Folder 19)
      - College themes, 2014 (Box 127, Folder 20)
      - Commonwealth Fund Proposal - Cornell Institute for Translational Research on Aging, 2006 (Box 127, Folder 21)
      - Cornell Center for Healthy Futures, 2014 (Box 127, Folder 22)
      - Cornell University Council Administrative Board, 2011-2012 (Box 127, Folder 23)
      - Cornell University Council Administrative Board orientation materials, 2013-2014 (Box 127, Folder 24)
      - Dean's initiative on health communication topics, 2009 (Box 127, Folder 25)
      - eCornell stats course for Sloan Program, 2009 (Box 127, Folder 26)
      - Early Childhood Center (ECCC), 2002-2004 (Box 127, Folder 27)
      - ECCC New Discoveries Infant and Toddler Center business plan, 2004 (Box 127, Folder 28)
      - ECCC Early Childhood Advisory Committee, 2005-2007 (Box 127, Folder 29)
      - ECCC logistics team, 2006-2008 (Box 127, Folder 30)
      - ECCC New York State childcare regulations, 2007 (Box 127, Folder 31)
      - Bright Horizons Child Care Center, 2008-2015 (Box 127, Folder 32)
      - Faculty Advisory Committee on Research and Education, 2007-2008 (Box 127, Folder 33)
      - Faculty Multi-Department Pilot Award Program, 2008-2009 (Box 127, Folder 34)
      - Faculty Multi-Department Pilot Award Program, 2009-2010 (Box 127, Folder 35)
      - Faculty Work Life survey results, 2006-11 (Box 127, Folder 36)
      - Family Life Development Center review and response, 2006 (Box 127, Folder 37)
      - Family Life Development Center Residential Child Care Project, 2005 (Box 127, Folder 38)
      - Family Life Development Center budget, 2008 (Box 127, Folder 39)
      - Family Life Development Center RC03: Behavior Management, Crisis Prevention and Intervention in Residential Settings, 2006 (Box 127, Folder 40)
      - Fashion Studies M.A. in New York City, 2013-2014 (Box 127, Folder 41)
      - Fashion Studies M.A. in New York City, 2013 (Box 127, Folder 42)
      - Fashion Studies M.A. - planning, 2014-2015 (Box 127, Folder 43)
      - Fashion Studies M.A. in New York City - proposals, vision session, 2013-2014 (Box 127, Folder 44)
      - Fashion Studies M.A. in New York City - proposals, vision session, 2013 (Box 127, Folder 45)
      - Human Development and the move of the Family Development Credential (FDC) to Temple University, 2009 (Box 127, Folder 46)
      - Human Developoment and the School Age Care Credential, 2005 (Box 127, Folder 47)
      - Human Development and the Henry Ricciuti Lecture Series, 2004 (Box 127, Folder 48)
      - Human Development and Therapeutic Crisis Intervention, 2008 (Box 127, Folder 49)
      - Grunwald's book "The Irresistible Henry House" based on research on Cornell's practice apartments and babies, 2010 (Box 127, Folder 50)
      - Migrant Program, 2004-2012 (Box 128, Folder 1)
      - Policies, general, 1998-2004 (Box 128, Folder 3)
      - Public speaking contest - Elsie Van Buren Rice, 2014 (Box 128, Folder 4)
      - Research program survey, 2006-2009 (Box 128, Folder 5)
      - Sloan Program, 2011-2015 (Box 128, Folder 6)
      - Sloan alumni letter, 2014 (Box 128, Folder 7)
      - Sustainability Action Plan, 2008-02 (Box 128, Folder 8)
      - Sustainability, 2009-2010 (Box 128, Folder 9)
      - Translational Science Center at Weill, Undated (Box 128, Folder 10)
      - Web redesign, 2005 (Box 128, Folder 11)
    - 2. Chairs and Deans Meetings
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 2009-2010 (Box 128, Folder 12)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 2013-02-2014-05 (Box 128, Folder 13)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 2015-09-2016-09 (Box 128, Folder 14)
      - Chairs and Deans Meetings, 2014-07-2015-05 (Box 128, Folder 15)
    - 3. Memoranda of Understanding
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and the College of Architecture, Art and Planning about shared space, 2013 (Box 128, Folder 16)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and Albany College of Pharmacy, 2008-2009 (Box 128, Folder 17)
      - Between DNS and Bassett Research Institute, 2007-2008 (Box 128, Folder 18)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and the College of Agriculture and Life Sciences about Mann Library space, 2013 (Box 128, Folder 19)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and the College of Agriculture and Life Sciences about shared support of DNS, 2007 (Box 128, Folder 20)
      - Bteween the Sloan Program and Catholic Health Initiatives, 2014-02-2015-05 (Box 128, Folder 21)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and the Cornell Child Care Center, 2008 (Box 128, Folder 22)
      - Between the Department of Policy Analysis and Management and the Cornell Cooprative Extension Association of Tompkins County, 2008 (Box 128, Folder 23)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and the Division of Alumni Affairs and Development, 2009 (Box 128, Folder 24)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and the Cornell University Library, 2014-10-06 (Box 128, Folder 25)
      - Between DNS and the College of Human Ecology and the College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, 2009-2012 (Box 128, Folder 26)
      - Between the Sloan Program and eCornell stats module, 2001-2007 (Box 128, Folder 27)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and the School of Hotel Administration, 2013-2015 (Box 128, Folder 28)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and Langmuir Lab, 2009-2011 (Box 128, Folder 29)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and Mann Library, 2008 (Box 128, Folder 30)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology, Coarnell University Institute for Policy Research (CUIPR) and the Medstat Group, 2003-2007 (Box 128, Folder 31)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and New York State Community Colleges, 1980-1996 (Box 128, Folder 32)
      - Between Cornell and the New York State Department of Social Services, 1994, 2002 (Box 128, Folder 33)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and SUNY Schools, 1980-2012 (Box 128, Folder 34)
      - Between Cornell and Syracuse University concerning the Upstate Population Research Consortium, 2013-2018 (Box 128, Folder 35)
      - Between Cornell and the United Nations University, 2007-2011 (Box 128, Folder 36)
      - Between Cornell and the Department of Veterans Affairs, 2005- (Box 128, Folder 37)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and the Department of Surgery at Weill, 2008 (Box 128, Folder 38)
      - Between DNS and World Hunger Education Services, 2015 (Box 128, Folder 39)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and Kyoritsu Woen's Educational Institution in Tokyo, 2007-2012 (Box 128, Folder 40)
      - Between the Dept. of Fiber Science and Apparel Design and Shinshu University in Japan, 2013-2018 (Box 128, Folder 41)
      - Between the Division of Nutritional Sciences and the National University of Malaysia, 2007-2012 (Box 128, Folder 42)
      - Between the Division of Nutritional Sciences and Instituto National de Salud Publica in Mexico, 2008-2012 (Box 128, Folder 43)
      - Between the Dept. of Design and Environmental Analysis and University of Nis, 2009-2014 (Box 128, Folder 44)
      - Between the Dept. of Design and Environmental Analysis and Hanyang University in the Republic of Korea, 2014-2021 (Box 128, Folder 45)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and the University of South Wales in Australia, 2009-2014 (Box 128, Folder 46)
      - Between the Dept. of Fiber Science and Apparel Design and Donghua University in China, 2013-2018 (Box 128, Folder 47)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and the Hong Kong Polytechnic University, 2006-2016 (Box 128, Folder 48)
      - Between the Family Life Development Center and Pontificia Universidad Javeriana in Colombia, 2010-2012 (Box 128, Folder 49)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and El Centro de Estudios de la Realidad Natural, Economica y Social in the Dominican Republic, 2014-2019 (Box 128, Folder 50)
      - Between the Division of Nutritional Sciences and the Ethiopian Health and Nutrition Research Institute, 2013-2018 (Box 128, Folder 51)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and l'Ecole nationale superieure des Arts Deocratifs in France, 2011-2017 (Box 128, Folder 52)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and Universite Paris-Sud, no date (Box 128, Folder 53)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and the University of Ghana, 2009-2013 (Box 128, Folder 54)
      - Between the Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections and Arogyavaram Medical Center in India, 2013=2018 (Box 128, Folder 55)
      - Between the Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections and the St. John's Research Institute in India, 2013-2018 (Box 128, Folder 56)
      - Between the Division of Nutritional Sciences and the Centre for the Study of Social Climate in India, 2015 (Box 128, Folder 57)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and Swami Vivekananda Youth Movement in India, 2013-2016 (Box 128, Folder 58)
      - Between the Division of Nutritional Sciences and S.N.D.T. Women's University in India, 2014-2019 (Box 128, Folder 59)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and Universita Commerciale "Luigi Bocconi" in Italy, 2014-2015 (Box 128, Folder 60)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and Korea Institute of Energy Research, 2010-2015 (Box 128, Folder 61)
      - Between the Cornell Institute for Public Affairs and Korea International Cooperation Agency in Seoul, 2016 (Box 128, Folder 62)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and Seoul National University, 2013-2018 (Box 128, Folder 63)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and Seoul National University, 1999-2008 (Box 128, Folder 64)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and the Yonsei University in Seoul, 2012-2018 (Box 128, Folder 65)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and the Unversity of Geneva, 1996-1997 (Box 128, Folder 66)
      - Between the Division of Nutritional Sciences and Mwanza Research Center in Tanzania, 2012-2013 (Box 128, Folder 67)
      - Between the Division of Nutritional Sciences and Kilimanjaro Christian Medical University College in Tanzania, 2009-2011 (Box 128, Folder 68)
      - Between the Division of Nutritional Sciences and Mahidol University in Thailand, 2007-2012 (Box 128, Folder 69)
      - Between the Dept. of Design and Environmental Analysis and Bartlett School of Graduate Studies, UK, 2010 (Box 128, Folder 70)
      - Between the College of Human Ecology and the University of Zambia, 2013-2018 (Box 128, Folder 71)
    - 4. Speeches
      - Speeches and presentations, 2009-2010 (Box 127, Folder 3)
      - Speeches and presentations, 2010-2011 (Box 127, Folder 4)
- Series III. Committee Files
  - A. Academic Status
    - Summary of Actions Taken, Minutes: January-May 1980, September-December 1979, Guidelines for Committee on Academic Status Annual Report 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Summary of Actions Taken, Minutes: January-May 1981, August-December 1980, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Summary of Actions Taken, Minutes: August-December, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Minutes: January-May 1983, August-December 1982, Summary of Actions Taken, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Minutes, Correspondence, Summary of Actions Taken, Annual Report 1982-1983, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Summary of Actions Taken, Correspondence, Minutes: August-May, Minutes: August-May, Summary of Actions Taken, 1984-1985, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Minutes, Summaries of Actions Taken, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Summary of Actions Taken: Spring 1987, Minutes, Summary of Actions Taken, 1986-1987, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Minutes, Summaries of Actions Taken, 1987-1988, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - B. Educational Policy
    - Index of Minutes, List of Minutes, Minutes, Annual Report (1964-1965), 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Minutes: March, April, Correspondence regarding S-U grade option, Report of Sub-Committee on ADA Curriculum for the Purpose of Re-Examining the Summer Practicum, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Minutes: May, Study No.1: Subject Matter Interests of Class of 1965, Study No. 2: The Distribution of Credits Taken by the Class of 1965, Study No.3: A Study of the Freshmen Applications for September 1965, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Index of Minutes, Annual Report 1966-1967, List of Members, Minutes: October, November, Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Development of a Policy Regarding Course Requirements for two-year Pre-Nursing Students, Correspondence, Minutes: November, December, January, February, March, Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Minutes: March, April, Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Minutes: May, Program Design for the Preparation of Teachers in Home Economics, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Minutes: May, June, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Annual Report, List of Members, Minutes: September, October, Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Minutes: November, Campus Academic Plan, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Revised Campus Academic Plan, Correspondence, Minutes: November, December, January, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Campus Academic Plans-I and II and Campus Development Plans for 1968 for the New York State College of Home Economics (Box 6, Folder 11A)
    - Minutes: February, Course Requirements for Majors in Home Economics, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Minutes: February, March, April, Graduation Requirements, Report of the Ad Hoc Committee on Teacher Preparation in the College of Home Economics, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - General Reports and Correspondence, Graduation Requirements- all majors, Minutes: April, May, Annual Report, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Annual Report, Correspondence, Minutes: October, November, December, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Memoranda, Report of the Placement of Bureau, Minutes: February, March, May, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Index, Annual Report, Correspondence, Major Requirements- all majors, Minutes: September, October, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Minutes: October, November, December, Correspondence, Summary of Course Evaluation Form, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Minutes: December, January, February, Correspondence, Major Requirements-all majors, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Minutes: February, March, April, Interdepartmental Major Requirements, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Minutes: May, Report of the Committee to Prepare a Proposal for a community service education major in the community service education department, Requirements for Community Service Education Major, Basic ADA Requirements, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Index of Minutes, Minutes: May, September, October, November, December, January, February, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Report of the Ad Hoc Committee to Develop Guidelines for Field Experience, Minutes: March, April, May, June, Annual Report 1968-1969, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Index of Minutes, Minutes: September, October, November, December, January, February, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Minutes: March, April, May, Report from the Ad Hoc Committee on 15 credit hours in Human Ecology outside the major, Agenda: February 27, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Minutes: September, October, November, December, January, Memorandum regarding Student Diversity, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Memo regarding Meeting on January 26, Human Ecology in the Field: A 5 Year Plan, SUNY Master Plan-1972, Minutes: January, February, Correspondence regarding R Grading Designation, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Minutes: March, April, May, Memorandum regarding Relevant Changes in the College, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Minutes: September, October, November, December, January, February, Memorandum regarding Missing Grades on Term Reports: Fall 1973 and Spring 1974, Report regarding: Changes in the Majors CSE and DEA, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Minutes: February, March, April, May, June, Correspondence regarding: Interdepartmental Courses, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Index of Minutes, Annual Report on Student Petitions: 1974-1975, Minutes: August, September, October, November, December, Memorandum: Revision of NS Honors Program, position Paper on Undergraduate and Graduate Education in the College of Human Ecology (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Minutes: January, February, March, April, May, Response to Position Paper (see folder 31), correspondence concerning: Undergraduate research, Report: The Biology and Society Curriculum, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Annual Report 1974-1975, Annual Report 1974-1974: Resident Instruction, Annual Report 1974-1975: The Student Body (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Index of Minutes, Annual Report 1975-76, Annual Report on Student Petitions: 1975-1976, Minutes: August, September, October, November, December, January, February, March, April, May, June (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Minutes: September, October, November, December, January, February, March, April, May, Annual Report 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Minutes: September, October, November, December, January, February, General Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Minutes: March, April, May, General Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Index of Minutes, Minutes: September, October, November, December, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - General Correspondence, Minutes: December, January, February, March, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - General Correspondence, Minutes: March, April, May, August, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Recommendations, Minutes: September, October, November, Summary Report, Correspondence: Bill Gauger, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Petitions to the Committee, General Correspondence, Minutes: December, Correspondence: Consumer Economics and Housing's 15 credit hour requirement, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Minutes: February, March, Proposed Admission Policy Statement, Design and Environmental Analysis-15 credit Requirement, Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Minutes: May (1979), March, April, May, September, October (1980), Annual Report 1979-1980, 1979-1980, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Re: Writing Competency, Correspondence Re: Apparel Design Curriculum, Minutes: October, Biology and Society Information, General Correspondence, Preliminary Report, Ad Hoc Committee on Basic Competencies in Communication, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Review of College Field Study Programs Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 3)